American Civil Liberties Union Records: Subgroup 2, Organizational Matters Series, 1947-1995: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 1: Organizational Matters, 1930-1995; 582 boxes
  - Subseries 1C: Board Committees, 1941-1990; 102 boxes
    - National Advisory Council, Minutes, 1978; 1 folder (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - National Development Council, Minutes and Correspondence, 1978; 1 folder (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Nominating Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1978; 1 folder (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Pension Committee, Minutes, Correspondence and Related Material, 1978; 1 folder (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Privacy Committee, Roster and Minutes, 1978; 1 folder (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Privacy Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1978; 1 folder (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Constitutional Rights and Economic Benefits, Special Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1978; 1 folder (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Constitutional Rights and Economic Benefits, Special Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1978; 1 folder (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Implementation of Policy on Constitutional Questions Involving Exclusion of, 1978; 1 folder (Box 121, Folder 11)
    - Nominating Committee, Special, Minutes and Correspondence, 1978; 1 folder (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - Regulation of Scientific Research, Special Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1978; 1 folder (Box 121, Folder 13)
    - Special Organizational Review Committee (SORC) Recommendations on Subject-Matter Committees, Miscellaneous, 1978; 1 folder (Box 121, Folder 14)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Minutes, 1979; 1 folder (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1979; 1 folder (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Affirmative Action Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1979; 1 folder (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Biennial Conference Review Committee, Minutes, 1979; 1 folder (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Biennial Conference Review Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1979; 2 folders (Box 122, Folder 5-6)
    - Church-State Committee, Roster and Minutes, 1979; 1 folder (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Church-State Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1979; 1 folder (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Communications Media Committee, Minutes, 1979; 1 folder (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Communications Media Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1979; 1 folder (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Constitutional Rights and Economic Benefits Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1979; 1 folder (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - Due Process Committee, Roster and Minutes, 1979; 1 folder (Box 122, Folder 12)
    - Due Process Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1979; 1 folder (Box 122, Folder 13)
    - Equality Committee, Minutes, 1979; 1 folder (Box 122, Folder 14)
    - Equality Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1979; 1 folder (Box 122, Folder 15)
    - Executive Committee, Minutes, 1979; 1 folder (Box 122, Folder 16)
    - Executive Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1979; 1 folder (Box 122, Folder 17)
    - Executive Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1979; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Free Speech/Association, Minutes, 1979; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Free Speech/Association, Correspondence and related materials, 1979; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - National Development Council Steering Committee, Minutes, 1979; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Nominating Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1979; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Pension Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1979; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Privacy Committee, Minutes, 1979; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Privacy Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1979; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Publications Committee, Minutes, Correspondence and Related Material, 1979; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Affirmative Action Policy, Special, Correspondence and related materials, 1979; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Government Regulation of Advertising, Special Committee, Roster and Minutes, 1979; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Government Regulation of Advertising, Special Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1979; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - Nominating Committee, Special, Minutes and Correspondence, 1979; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1980; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Affirmative Action Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1980; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Budget Audit Investment, Minutes and Correspondence, 1980; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Biennial Conference Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1980; 2 folders (Box 124, Folder 4-5)
    - Building Fund Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1980; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Church-State Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1980; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Communications Media Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1980; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Constitution Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1980; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Due Process Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1980; 1 folder (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Equality Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1980; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Executive Committee, Minutes, 1980; 1 folder (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Executive Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1980; 6 folders (Box 125, Folder 3-8)
    - Executive Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1980; 3 folders (Box 126, Folder 1-3)
    - Free Speech/Association, Minutes and Correspondence, 1980; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Financial Structures Committee, Minutes, 1980; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Indian Rights Committee, Minutes, 1980; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - National Development Council, Minutes, 1980; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Nominating Committee, Minutes, 1980; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Publications Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1980; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Pension Committee, Minutes, 1980; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - Arrest Records, Special Committee, Minutes, 1980; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - Government Regulations on Advertising, Special, Minutes, 1980; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - Medical Experimentation on Human Subjects, Special Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1980; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 13)
    - Televising Courtroom Proceeding, Special Committee, Minutes, 1980; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 14)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Minutes, 1981; 1 folder (Box 126, Folder 15)
    - Budget Audit Investigation, Correspondence and related materials, 1981; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Church State, Minutes and Correspondence, 1981; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Communications Media Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1981; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Communications Media, Minutes and Correspondence, 1981; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Constitution Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1981; 2 folders (Box 127, Folder 5-6)
    - Due Process Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1981; 2 folders (Box 127, Folder 7-8)
    - Equality Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1981; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Executive Committee, Minutes, 1981; 1 folder (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - Executive Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1981; 7 folders (Box 128, Folder 1-7)
    - Free Speech/Association, Minutes, 1981; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Free Speech/Association, Correspondence and related materials, 1981; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - Nominating Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1981; 3 folders (Box 129, Folder 1-3)
    - Nominating Committee, Special, Minutes and Correspondence, 1981; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - National Development Council, Minutes, 1981; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Pension Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1981; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Privacy Committee, Minutes, 1981; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Privacy Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1981; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Publications Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1981; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Affirmative Action Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1981; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Arrest Records, Special Board Committees, Minutes and Correspondence, 1981; 1 folder (Box 129, Folder 11)
    - Board Composition and Structure, Special Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1981; 2 folders (Box 129, Folder 12-13)
    - Board Structure and Composition, Special Committee on, Minutes and Correspondence, 1981; 2 folders (Box 130, Folder 1-2)
    - Building Fund Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1981; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Cable TV Subcommittee, Correspondence and related materials, 1981; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Cable TV Subcommittee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1981; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Government Regulations in Advertising, Special, Minutes and Correspondence, 1981; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Medical Experimentation on Human Subjects, Minutes and Correspondence, 1981; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Private Pressure Groups, Special Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1981; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Special Board Committee on Rights of Elem., Minutes and Correspondence, 1981; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - Televising Court Room Proceedings, Special Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1981; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Use of Public Property by Religious Groups, Special, Minutes and Correspondence, 1981; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - ACLU Subject Matter Committees, Correspondence and related materials, 1982; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 13)
    - Affirmative Action Committee, Minutes, 1982; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - Biennial Conference Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 2 folders (Box 131, Folder 1-2)
    - Church/State Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Communications Media Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 2 folders (Box 131, Folder 4-5)
    - Constitution Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Due Process Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 1 folder (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Due Process Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Equality Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Executive Committee, Minutes, 1982; 1 folder (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Executive Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1982; 4 folders (Box 132, Folder 4-7)
    - Free Speech/Association, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 2 folders (Box 133, Folder 1-2)
    - Indian Rights, Roster, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - National Development Steering Committee, Minutes, 1982; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Nominating Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 2 folders (Box 133, Folder 5-6)
    - Nominating Committee, Special, Correspondence and related materials, 1982; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Pension Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Privacy Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Board Structure and Composition, Special, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Cable TV Subcommittee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - Financial Structures Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Government Regulation of Advertising, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Grand Jury Policy, Special, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - International Civil Liberties (Policy #401), Special Committee on, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - International Civil Liberties, Special, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 1 folder (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Political Campaign Financing, Special, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 3 folders (Box 134, Folder 6-8)
    - Political Campaign Financing, Special, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 3 folders (Box 135, Folder 1-3)
    - Report Budget Cuts, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Uniform Accounting Procedures, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Warrantless Searches, Minutes and Correspondence, 1982; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1983; 1 folder (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - Biennial Conference Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1983; 2 folders (Box 135, Folder 8-9)
    - Church/State Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1983; 1 folder (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Constitution Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1983; 1 folder (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Communication Media Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1983; 2 folders (Box 136, Folder 3-4)
    - Due Process Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1983; 2 folders (Box 136, Folder 5-6)
    - Equality Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1983; 1 folder (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Executive Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1983; 5 folders (Box 137, Folder 1-5)
    - Free Speech/Association, Minutes and Correspondence, 1983; 1 folder (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Free Speech/Association, Minutes and Correspondence, 1983; 1 folder (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Privacy Committee, Minutes, 1983; 1 folder (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Nominating Committee, Minutes, 1983; 1 folder (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Nominating Committee, Special, Minutes, 1983; 1 folder (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Pension Committee, Minutes, 1983; 1 folder (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Arrest Records Committee, Special, Minutes, 1983; 1 folder (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Board Diversity Committee, Special, Minutes, 1983; 1 folder (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Cable TV Committee, Special, Minutes, 1983; 1 folder (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Government Regulation of Advertising, Special, Minutes, 1983; 1 folder (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - International Civil Liberties (Policy #401) Review, Special, Minutes, 1983; 1 folder (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Televising Courtroom Proceedings Committee, Special, Minutes, 1983; 1 folder (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - Courtroom Proceedings Committee, Special, Minutes, 1983; 1 folder (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - Courtroom Proceedings Committee, Special (working papers), Minutes, 1983; 1 folder (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Courtroom Broadcasting and Photography, Special, Minutes, 1983; 3 folders (Box 139, Folder 2-4)
    - International Civil Liberties (Policy #401), Special, Minutes, 1983; 1 folder (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Poverty and Civil Liberties Committee, Minutes, 1983; 1 folder (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - Political Campaign Committee, Special, Minutes, 1983; 1 folder (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - Political Campaign Financing Committee, Special, Minutes, 1983; 3 folders (Box 140, Folder 1-3)
    - Academic Freedom Clearing House, Minutes, 1983; 1 folder (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Minutes, 1984; 2 folders (Box 140, Folder 5-6)
    - Affirmative Action, Minutes, 1984; 1 folder (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Biennial Conference Committee, Minutes, 1985; 1 folder (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Biennial Conference Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1985; 1 folder (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - Biennial Conference Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1984; 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Board Composition and Diversity Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1984; 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Church/State Committee, Minutes, 1984; 2 folders (Box 141, Folder 3-4)
    - Communications Media Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1984; 4 folders (Box 141, Folder 5-8)
    - Constitution Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1984; 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Due Process Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1984; 1 folder (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Due Process Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1984; 2 folders (Box 142, Folder 1-2)
    - Equality Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1984; 2 folders (Box 142, Folder 3-4)
    - Executive Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1984; 4 folders (Box 142, Folder 5-8)
    - Executive Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1984; 2 folders (Box 143, Folder 1-2)
    - Free Speech/Association, Minutes and Correspondence, 1984; 2 folders (Box 143, Folder 3-4)
    - Nominating Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1984; 2 folders (Box 143, Folder 5-6)
    - Nominating Committee, Special, Minutes, 1984; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Pension Committee, Minutes, 1984; 1 folder (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Privacy Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1984; 2 folders (Box 144, Folder 1-2)
    - Nuclear Arms and Civil Liberties Committee, Special, Minutes and Correspondence, 1984; 5 folders (Box 144, Folder 3-7)
    - Political Campaign Financing Special Committee, Minutes and Correspondence, 1984; 4 folders (Box 145, Folder 1-4)
    - Poverty and Civil Liberties, Special, Minutes and Correspondence, 1984; 2 folders (Box 145, Folder 5-6)
    - Racially Exclusive Facilities, Special, Minutes, 1984; 1 folder (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Receiving and Withholding of Medical Treatment, Special, Minutes, 1984; 1 folder (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Use of Public Property for Religious Purposes (Policy #95), Special, Minutes, 1984; 1 folder (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Minutes, 1985; 1 folder (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1985; 1 folder (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Affirmative Action, Correspondence and related materials, 1985; 1 folder (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Biennial Conference Committee, Minutes, 1985; 1 folder (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Biennial Conference Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1985; 1 folder (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Church/State, Minutes, 1985; 1 folder (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Church/State Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1985; 2 folders (Box 146, Folder 7-8)
    - Communications Media Committee, Minutes, 1985; 1 folder (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - Communications Media Comm., Membership Roster and Correspondence, 1985; 1 folder (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - Communications Media Comm., Membership Roster and Correspondence, 1985; 1 folder (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Constitution Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1985; 1 folder (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Due Process Committee, Minutes, 1985; 1 folder (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Due Process Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1985; 2 folders (Box 147, Folder 4-5)
    - Equality Committee, Minutes, 1985; 1 folder (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Equality Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1985; 2 folders (Box 147, Folder 7-8)
    - Executive Committee, Minutes, 1985; 1 folder (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Executive Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1985; 5 folders (Box 148, Folder 2-6)
    - Free Speech/Association, Minutes, 1985; 1 folder (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Free Speech/Association, Correspondence and related materials, 1985; 1 folder (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Nominating Committee, Minutes, 1985; 1 folder (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Nominating Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1985; 2 folders (Box 149, Folder 4-5)
    - Nominating Committee, Special, Miscellaneous, 1985; 1 folder (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Pension Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1985; 1 folder (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Privacy Committee, Minutes, 1985; 1 folder (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Privacy Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1985; 2 folders (Box 149, Folder 9-10)
    - Political Campaign Financing Committee, Special, Correspondence and related materials, 1985; 1 folder (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Poverty and Constitutional Rights, Miscellaneous, 1985; 1 folder (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Receiving and Withholding of Medical Treatment, Special, Miscellaneous, 1985; 2 folders (Box 150, Folder 3-4)
    - Scientific Research Committee, Special, Minutes, 1985; 1 folder (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Scientific Research Committee, Special, Correspondence and related materials, 1985; 1 folder (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Warrantless Searches Committee, Special, Correspondence and related materials, 1985; 1 folder (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Minutes, 1986; 1 folder (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Academic Freedom Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1986; 2 folders (Box 151, Folder 1-2)
    - Affirmative Action Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1986; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Biennial Conference Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1986; 2 folders (Box 151, Folder 4-5)
    - Church/State Committee, Minutes, 1986; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Church/State Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1986; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Communications Media Committee, Minutes, 1986; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Communications Media Committee, Correspondence and other materials, 1986; 1 folder (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Communications Media Committee, Correspondence and other materials, 1986; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Constitution Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1986; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Due Process Committee, Minutes, 1986; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Due Process Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1986; 3 folders (Box 152, Folder 4-6)
    - Equality Committee, Minutes, 1986; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Equality Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1986; 1 folder (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Equality Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1986; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Executive Committee, Minutes, 1986; 1 folder (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Executive Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1986; 4 folders (Box 153, Folder 3-6)
    - Executive Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1986; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Free Speech/Association, Minutes, 1986; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Free Speech/Association, Correspondence and related materials, 1986; 2 folders (Box 154, Folder 3-4)
    - Indian Rights Committee, Minutes, 1986; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Nominating Committee, Minutes, 1986; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Nominating Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1986; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - Nominating Committee, Special, Minutes, 1986; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - Nominating Committee, Special, Correspondence and related materials, 1986; 1 folder (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - Pension Committee, Minutes, 1986; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Pension Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1986; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Privacy Committee, Minutes, 1986; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Privacy Committee, Correspondence and related materials, 1986; 2 folders (Box 155, Folder 4-5)
    - Abortion Policy Committee, Special, Minutes, 1986; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Abortion Policy Committee, Special, Correspondence and other materials, 1986; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Position on World Court, Special, Correspondence and related materials, 1986; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - English-only Movement, Special, Correspondence and related materials, 1986; 1 folder (Box 155, Folder 9)